Privacy
=======

**Effective Date:** January 1, 2024

To download and/or print this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”), click [here](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/uploads/pdf/privacy-policy.pdf).

**Privacy Policy Scope**

Welcome! This Privacy Policy applies to your use of any online services (e.g., website, software, or mobile app, and certain e-mails we send) that posts a link to this Privacy Policy, regardless of how you access or use it. Click [here](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/terms-of-use/) to view our Terms of Use.

**Questions and How to Contact Landmark Properties**

For more information about Landmark Properties’ privacy practices regarding the Service, read our Privacy Policy. You can also contact Landmark Properties [here](mailto:Privacy@landmarkproperties.com) if you have questions or concerns.

**Table of Contents**

For a clickable table of contents that will help you find and navigate to all the sections of the Privacy Policy click [here](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#main-table-contents).

**Print this Privacy Policy**

To see and print our Privacy Policy, click [here](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/uploads/pdf/privacy-policy.pdf).

**LANDMARK PROPERTIES PRIVACY POLICY**

Thank you for visiting an online service that posts a link to this Privacy Policy (“**Service**”) owned or operated by Landmark Properties, Inc. d/b/a LMK Properties, Inc. or one of its Affiliates (defined below) (“**Landmark Properties**”, “**we**”, or “**us**” or “**our**”). This Privacy Policy will provide you with information as to how Landmark Properties collects, uses, and discloses information about you, including the choices Landmark Properties offers with respect to that information, and applies to your use of any Service, regardless of how you access or use it. It does not apply to Landmark Properties’ data collection activities offline or otherwise outside of the Service (unless otherwise stated below or at the time of collection). For certain Services, there may be additional notices about information practices and choices. Please read those additional privacy disclosures to understand how they apply to you.

By visiting or otherwise using the Service, you agree to the Service’s [Terms of Use](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/terms-of-use/) and consent to Landmark Properties’ data collection, use, and disclosure practices, and other activities as described in this Privacy Policy, and any additional privacy statements that may be posted on an applicable part of the Service. If you do not agree and consent, please discontinue use of the Service, and uninstall Service downloads and applications.

1. **INFORMATION WE COLLECT**
    
    1. **Information about You that You Provide.**
        
        Landmark Properties, and/or its Service Providers (defined below), may collect information you provide directly to Landmark Properties and/or its Service Providers via the Service. For example, Landmark Properties collects information when you use or register for the Service, subscribe to notifications, post on the Service, participate in promotional activities, or communicate or transact through the Service. In addition, when you interact with Third-Party Services (defined below), you may be able to provide information to those third parties. For more information on Third-Party Services’ data collection and practices click [here](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#third-party-content). For more information on Service Provider data collection and practices click [here](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#info-we-share).
        
        Information Landmark Properties, its Service Providers and/or Third-Party Services may collect includes: (1) personal information, which is information that relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with you or your household, such as your first and last name, e-mail address, phone number, address, Social Security number, government-issued identification number, education or employment information, criminal history, vehicle information, and full payment account number (“**Personal Information**” or “**PI**”); (2) demographic information, such as your gender, age, citizenship, zip code, interests, and recent and upcoming purchases (“**Demographic Information**”); and (3) commercial information such as your apartment preferences, desired budget, lease term, move-in date, and any additional information you wish to provide (“**Commercial Information**”).
        
        “**De–identified information**” i.e., information that cannot reasonably be used to infer information about, or otherwise be linked to, a particular person or household because of the removal or modification of the personally identifiable elements, or the extraction of non-personally identifiable elements including through anonymization, pseudonymization, and/or hashing, is not Personal Information and may be used and shared without obligation to you, except as prohibited by applicable law. We will not attempt to reidentify Personal Information that has been de-identified except to confirm that our de-identification process is sufficient to render the underlying information unlinkable to a particular person or household.
        
    2. **Information Collected Automatically**
        
        Landmark Properties, its Service Providers, and/or Third-Party Services may also automatically collect certain information about you when you access or use the Service (“Usage Information”). Usage Information may include IP address, device identifier, browser type, operating system, information about your use of the Service, and data regarding network connected hardware (_e.g._, computer or mobile device). For more information on Third-Party Services’ data collection and practices click [here](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#third-party-content). For more information on Service Provider data collection and practices click [here](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#info-we-share). For information on choices some of these third parties may offer you regarding automated data collection click [here](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#choices-options).
        
        The methods that may be used on the Service to collect Usage Information include:
        
        * **Log Information**: Log information is data about your use of the Service, such as IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamps, and related data, and may be stored in log files.
        * **Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**: Cookies, web beacons (also known as “tracking pixels”), embedded scripts, location-identifying technologies, device recognition technologies, device and activity monitoring and other tracking technologies now and hereafter developed (“**Tracking Technologies**”) may be used to collect information about interactions with the Service or e-mails, including information about your browsing and purchasing behavior.
        * Cookies
            * A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s device, which may last for a session or be persistent. Session cookies make it easier for you to navigate the Service and expire when you close your browser. Persistent cookies remain longer and help in understanding how you use the Service and enhance your user experience. Persistent cookies may remain on your hard drive for an extended period of time. If you use your browser’s method of blocking or removing cookies, some but not all types of cookies may be deleted and/or blocked and as a result some features, and functionalities of the Service may not work.
        * Web Beacons (“Tracking Pixels”)
            * Web beacons are small graphic images, also known as “Internet tags” or “clear gifs,” embedded in web pages and e-mail messages. Web beacons may be used, without limitation, to count the number of visitors to the Service, to monitor how users navigate the Service, and to count content view.
        * Embedded Scripts
            * An embedded script is website code designed to collect information about your interactions with the Service. Embedded scripts may run while you are on our website.
        * Location-identifying Technologies
            * Geo-filtering and other location-aware technologies locate you, or make assumptions about your location, for purposes such as verifying your location and delivering or restricting content, including third-party ads, based on your location. If you have enabled GPS or use other location-based features on the Service, your device location may be tracked by us and third parties.
        * Device Recognition Technologies.
            * Technologies, including application of statistical probability to data sets, as well as linking a common unique identifier to different device use (e.g., Facebook ID), which attempt to recognize or make assumptions about users and devices (e.g., that a user of multiple devices is the same user or household) (“**Cross-device Data**”).
        * Device and Activity Monitoring
            * Technologies that monitor, and may record, certain of your interactions with the Service, including without limitation, keystrokes and mouse movements, and/or collect and analyze information from your device, such as, without limitation, your operating system, plug-ins, system fonts, and other data, for purposes such as identification, security, fraud prevention, troubleshooting, tracking and/or improving the Services and customizing or optimizing your experience on the Services. Records of your interactions collected by device and activity monitoring technologies may be disclosed to our vendors for the purposes of analytics, advertising, and Service functionality.
    3. **Information Landmark Properties Collects From Other Sources**
        
        Landmark Properties may collect Personal Information about you from other sources, including Service Providers and Third-Party Services.
        
2. **HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE OBTAIN**
    
    Landmark Properties may use Personal Information for any purposes not inconsistent with Landmark Properties’ statements under this Privacy Policy, or otherwise made by us in writing at the point of collection, and not prohibited by applicable law, including, without limitation, in order to:
    
    * Allow you to participate in the features we offer on the Service;
    * Facilitate, manage, personalize, and improve your online experience;
    * Process your registration and manage your account;
    * Transact with you, provide services or information you request, respond to your comments, questions and requests, serve you content and/or advertising, and send you notices;
    * Landmark Properties Affiliates’ marketing and other purposes;
    * Improve the Service and for any other internal business purposes;
    * Tailor our content, advertisements, and offers;
    * Fulfill other purposes disclosed at the time you provide Personal Information or otherwise where we are legally permitted or are required to do so;
    * Determine your location and manage digital content rights (e.g., territory restrictions); and
    * Prevent and address fraud, breach of policies or terms, and threats or harm.
3. **INFORMATION WE DISCLOSE TO THIRD PARTIES**
    
    Except as restricted by applicable law, Landmark Properties may share Personal Information with third parties or Landmark Properties affiliates (“**Affiliates**”) subject to the following:
    
    * Marketing: Subject to your communications choices explained [here](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#communications), and the rights of California residents explained [here](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#california-residents), we may use your Personal Information to send you marketing communications. Landmark Properties will not share your Personal Information with third parties, other than Affiliates, for their own direct marketing purposes, except in connection with Corporate Transactions (defined below) absent your consent (which may be by means of third-party interaction described in the next bullet point).
    
    Landmark Properties may also disclose Personal Information for any purposes not inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, or our written statements at the point of collection, and otherwise not prohibited by applicable law, including, without limitation:
    
    * Landmark Properties’ agents, vendors, consultants, and other service providers (collectively “Service Providers”) may receive, or be given access to, your Personal Information in connection with their work on Landmark Properties’ behalf. For more information on choices Service Providers may offer you click [here](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#choices-options).
    * To comply with the law, law enforcement or other legal process, and, where permitted, in response to a government request.
    * If Landmark Properties believes your actions are inconsistent with Landmark Properties’ terms of use, user agreements, applicable terms or policies, or to protect the rights, property, life, health, security and safety of Landmark Properties, the Service or its users, or any third party.
    
    In addition, Landmark Properties may disclose your Personal Information in connection with or during negotiations of any proposed or actual financing of our business, or merger, purchase, sale, joint venture, or any other type of acquisition or business combination of all or any portion of Landmark Properties assets, or transfer of all or a portion of Landmark Properties’ business to another company, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding (“Corporate Transactions”).
    
4. **SWEEPSTAKES, CONTESTS, AND PROMOTIONS**
    
    Landmark Properties may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (each, a “Promotion”), including Promotions jointly sponsored or offered by third parties, which may require submitting Personal Information. If you voluntarily choose to enter a Promotion, your Personal Information may be disclosed to Landmark Properties, co-sponsors, Service Providers, and other third parties, including for administrative purposes and as required by law (_e.g._, on a winners list). By entering, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that Promotion, which may include consent to additional or differing data practices from those contained in this Privacy Policy. Please review those rules carefully.
    
5. **THIRD-PARTY CONTENT AND SERVICES**
    
    The Service may include hyperlinks to websites, locations, platforms, applications or services operated by third parties (“**Third–Party Service(s)**”). These Third-Party Services may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other Tracking Technology to independently collect Personal Information. Landmark Properties has no control over Third-Party Services or their data collection and data use practices.
    
6. **ANALYTICS**
    
    Landmark Properties may use Google Analytics or other Service Providers for analytics services. These analytics services may use cookies and other Tracking Technologies to help Landmark Properties analyze Service users and how they use the Service. Information generated by these services (_e.g._, your IP address and other Usage Information) may be transmitted to and stored by these Service Providers on servers in the U.S. (or elsewhere) and these Service Providers may use this information for purposes such as evaluating your use of the Service, compiling statistic reports on the Service’s activity, and providing other services relating to Service activity and other internet usage.
    
    For more information on how Google Analytics uses data collected through our Services, visit [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners). To opt out of Google Analytics cookies, visit [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) or download the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-On.
    
7. **DATA SECURITY AND MONITORING**
    
    Landmark Properties takes reasonable measures to protect Personal Information from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Nevertheless, transmission via the internet and online digital storage are not completely secure and Landmark Properties does not guarantee the security of your information collected through the Service.
    
    To help protect you and others, Landmark Properties and its Service Providers may (but make no commitment to) monitor use of the Service, and may collect and use related information including Personal Information for all purposes not prohibited by applicable law or inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, including, without limitation, to identify fraudulent activities and transactions; prevent abuse of, and investigate and/or seek prosecution for, any potential threats to or misuse of the Service; ensure compliance with the [Terms of Use](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/terms-of-use/) and this Privacy Policy; investigate violations of or enforce these documents; improve the Services and your Services experiences, and to protect the rights and property of Landmark Properties, third parties, and other users. Monitoring may result in the collection, recording, and analysis of online activity or communications through our Service. If you do not consent to these conditions, you must discontinue your use of the Service.
    
8. **INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER**
    
    Landmark Properties is based in the U.S. and the information Landmark Properties and its Service Providers collect is governed by U.S. law. If you are located in the European Union (EU), European Economic Area (EEA), and/or Switzerland, please note that Landmark Properties does not intend to offer goods and services (including the Services) to EU, EEA, or Swiss individuals. If you are accessing the Service from outside of the U.S., please be aware that information collected through the Service may be transferred to, processed, stored, and used in the U.S. Data protection laws in the U.S. may be different from those of your country of residence. Your use of the Service or provision of any information therefore constitutes your consent to the transfer to and from, processing, usage, sharing, and storage of your information, including Personally Identifiable Information, in the U.S. as set forth in this Privacy Policy.
    
9. **CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**
    
    The Service is intended for a general audience and not directed to children less than sixteen (16) years of age.
    
    Landmark Properties does not intend to collect personal information as defined by the U.S. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“**COPPA**”) (“**Children’s Personal Information**”) in a manner that is not permitted by COPPA. If we obtain knowledge that we have collected Children’s Personal Information in a manner not permitted by COPPA, we will remove such data to the extent required by COPPA.
    
10. **ACCESSING AND CHANGING INFORMATION**
    
    Landmark Properties may provide web pages or other mechanisms allowing you to delete, correct, or update Personal Information (e.g., profile and account information). Landmark Properties will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in Landmark Properties’ then-active databases as soon as practicable, but it is not always possible to completely change, remove or delete all of your information or public postings from Landmark Properties’ databases and residual and/or cached data may remain archived thereafter. Further, we reserve the right to retain data (a) as required by applicable law; and (b) for so long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes for which the data is retained except to the extent prohibited by applicable law.
    
11. **Choices: Tracking and Communications Options**
    
    1. **Tracking Technologies Generally**
        
        Cookies may generally be disabled or removed by tools available as part of most commercial browsers, and in some instances blocked in the future by selecting certain settings. Browsers offer different functionalities and options, so you may need to set them separately. Please be aware that if you disable or remove these technologies, some parts of the Service may not work and that when you revisit the Service your ability to limit browser-based Tracking Technologies is subject to your browser settings and limitations.
        
        In addition, your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a “Do Not Track” signal to online services you visit. Like many online services, Landmark Properties currently does not alter Landmark Properties’ practices when Landmark Properties receives a “Do Not Track” signal from a visitor’s browser. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” you can visit [www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/), but Landmark Properties is not responsible for the completeness or accuracy of this third-party information.
        
    2. **Communications.**
        
        You can opt out of receiving certain promotional communications (emails or text messaging) from Landmark Properties at any time by (i) for promotional e-mails, following the instructions provided in emails to click on the unsubscribe link, or if available by changing your communication preferences by logging onto your account; (ii) for text messages, following the instructions provided in text messages to opt out; and (iii) for app push notifications, turn off push notifications on the settings of your device and/or the app, as applicable.
        
12. **STATE NOTICES**
    
    1. **California**
        
        This California Privacy Notice (“**Notice**”) is provided pursuant to the California Consumer Privacy Act, as amended (the “**CCPA**”), and describes how and why Landmark Properties, its affiliates, and subsidiaries (collectively, “**Landmark**”) collects, uses, and discloses Personal Information of California consumers (“**you**”), the rights afforded to you by the CCPA, and how to exercise those rights. This Notice does not apply to California job applicants, current and former employees, contractors, or beneficiaries. If you are a California consumer and interacted with us in one of these capacities, please contact us as provided below for more information.
        
        As used in this Notice, the term “**Personal Information**” means information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with you. Personal information does not include information that is publicly available, de-identified, or aggregated.
        
        Unless otherwise noted, the disclosures in this Notice cover our activities in the twelve (12) months prior to the Effective Date, as well as our current practices.
        
        1. **Collection, Use, and Disclosure of Personal Information**
            
            Landmark may collect, use, and disclose Personal Information for business purposes consistent with applicable laws as identified below. Where we transfer applicable Personal Information to recipients, such as our service providers, we do so for the same business purposes described below. These examples may vary depending on the nature of your interactions with us.
            
            | **Category of Personal Information** | **Purposes for Collection, Use, or Disclosure** | **Categories of Recipients to whom Personal Information is Disclosed** |
            | --- | --- | --- |
            | **Identifiers**, including real name, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, social security number, driver’s license number, state ID number, passport number, or other similar identifiers | * To communicate with you<br>* To manage and facilitate business operations, including transactions, advertising and marketing services, safety and security, fraud detection and prevention, quality assurance, and our websites<br>* To evaluate and improve our business operations<br>* To comply with legal obligations | * Service providers<br>* Affiliates<br>* Advertising providers<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* IT vendors |
            | **Personal information described in Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e),** including physical characteristics or description, signature, telephone number, date of birth, education, employment, bank account number, or any other financial information, medical information | * To communicate with you<br>* To manage and facilitate business operations, including transactions, advertising and marketing services, safety and security, fraud detection and prevention, quality assurance, and our websites<br>* To evaluate and improve our business operations<br>* To comply with legal obligations | * Service providers<br>* Affiliates<br>* IT vendors |
            | **Characteristics of protected classifications** under California or federal law, including age, citizenship, familial status, disability | * To comply with legal obligations<br>* To manage and facilitate business operations, including transactions, advertising and marketing services, safety and security, fraud detection and prevention, quality assurance, and our websites | * Service providers<br>* Affiliates |
            | **Commercial Information,** including the location and type of apartment, home, or building you are interested in, desired budget, lease term, and move-in date, whether you have pets, and any additional details you wish to provide | * To comply with legal obligations<br>* To manage and facilitate business operations, including transactions, advertising and marketing services, safety and security, fraud detection and prevention, quality assurance, and our websites | * Service providers<br>* Affiliates |
            | **Internet Usage Information,** including browsing, search, and usage histories | * To manage and facilitate business operations, including transactions, advertising and marketing services, safety and security, fraud detection and prevention, quality assurance, and our websites | * Service providers<br>* Affiliates<br>* Advertising providers<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Internet service providers<br>* IT vendors |
            | **Geolocation Data,** including physical location inferred from your IP address | * To manage and facilitate business operations, including transactions, advertising and marketing services, safety and security, fraud detection and prevention, quality assurance, and our websites | * Service providers<br>* Affiliates<br>* Advertising providers<br>* Data analytics providers<br>* Internet service providers<br>* IT vendors |
            | **Sensory Data**, including audio and/or visual recordings of customer care calls, and security cameras footage | * To manage and facilitate business operations, including transactions, safety and security, and fraud detection and prevention | * Service providers<br>* IT vendors |
            | **Professional or Employment Information,** including professional, educational, or employment-related information, including personal or professional references | * To comply with legal obligations<br>* To manage and facilitate business operations, including transactions, advertising and marketing services, safety and security, fraud detection and prevention, quality assurance, and our websites | * Service providers<br>* Affiliates |
            | **Non-public Education Records**, including education records directly related to a student maintained by an educational institution or party acting on its behalf, or student financial information | * To manage and facilitate business operations, including transactions, safety and security, fraud detection and prevention, and quality assurance | * Service providers<br>* Affiliates |
            | **Other Categories of Personal Information**, including national identification information, vehicle information, and criminal history | * To comply with legal obligations<br>* To manage and facilitate business operations, including transactions, safety and security, and fraud detection and prevention | * Service providers<br>* Affiliates |
            
        2. **Sources of Personal Information**
            
            We collect the Personal Information identified above from the following sources:
            
            * **Directly from you**. For example, during the purchase or rental application process, through our websites or online systems, and other processes where you may submit Personal Information to us.
            * **Automatically when using our digital services or visiting our premises**. For example, when you use our websites or online services, and when you access our facilities.
            * **Landmark affiliates**. For example, we receive Personal Information from our affiliates, as permitted, to enable us to manage our business.
            * **Parties to corporate transactions**. As permitted by law, we may receive Personal Information as part of a corporate transaction or proceeding such as a merger, financing, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, or at transfer, divestiture, or sale of all or a portion of a business or assets.
            * **Business partners**. We may receive information about you from service providers, business partners, or other vendors. For example, we may receive employment-related information about you from your references, or through a background check service provider.
        3. **Disclosing Your Personal Information**
            
            We may disclose each of the categories of Personal Information identified above to the respectively identified categories of recipients for operational or business purposes consistent with the purposes for collection or use designated, as is reasonably necessary and proportionate to achieve those purposes, or for another purpose that is compatible with the context in which the Personal Information was collected including, but not limited to:
            
            * Auditing ads;
            * Helping to ensure security and integrity;
            * Debugging, repairing, and improving functionality;
            * Short-term, transient use;
            * Performing services on our behalf;
            * Providing advertising and marketing services, as applicable;
            * Internal research for technological development; and
            * Verifying quality and/or safety.
            
            In addition to the other purposes for collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information described in this Notice, we may collect, use, and disclose Personal Information as required by law, regulation or court order; to respond to governmental and/or law enforcement requests; to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with our or others’ rights or property; to support any actual or threatened claim, defense or declaration in a case or before any jurisdictional and/or administrative authority, arbitration or mediation panel; or in connection with disciplinary actions/investigations. Likewise, we may use and disclose Personal Information to other parties in connection with a sale, assignment, merger, reorganization, or other transfer of Landmark.
            
        4. **Data Retention**
            
            We generally maintain Personal Information according to our retention obligations and policies, operational business purposes, and other legal and regulatory requirements. We discard this Personal Information when reasonably practicable.
            
            We keep the categories of Personal Information described above for as long as is necessary for the purposes described in this Notice or otherwise authorized by law. This generally means holding the information for as long as one of the following apply:
            
            * Your Personal Information is reasonably necessary to manage our operations, to manage your relationship with us, or to satisfy another purpose for which we collected it;
            * Your Personal Information is reasonably necessary to carry out a disclosed purpose that is reasonably compatible with the context in which it was collected;
            * Your Personal Information is reasonably required to protect or defend our rights or property (which will generally relate to applicable laws that limit actions in a particular case);
            * We are otherwise required or permitted to keep your Personal Information by applicable laws or regulations.
            
            Where your Personal Information is used for more than one purpose, we will retain it until the purpose with the latest period expires.
            
        5. **Sales and Sharing of Personal Information**
            
            We do not sell Personal Information in exchange for money, but some of the ways in which we share Personal Information may be considered a sale under the CCPA. We may sell and/or share the following categories of personal information with third parties for the purposes of cross-context behavioral advertising:
            
            * Identifiers
            * Internet or other electronic network activity
            * Geolocation data
            
            We sell and/or share this Personal Information with third parties for advertising purposes. The third parties to whom this Personal Information is sold and/or shared are advertisers and analytics vendors.
            
            California residents may opt out of sales and sharing of your Personal Information as set forth in the “Right to Opt Out of Sales and Sharing of Personal Information” section below.
            
            We do not have actual knowledge that we sell or share the personal information of consumers under sixteen (16) years of age.
            
        6. **California Privacy Rights**
            
            If you are a resident of California, you have the right to submit certain requests relating to your Personal Information as described below. To exercise any of these rights, please use our [Privacy Web Form (onetrust.com)](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/0680dcba-1e23-43d2-8969-1b3ed9c36860/1257ef14-eb99-4a7f-b9da-cf2f1838e626), email us at [privacy@landmarkproperties.com](mailto:privacy@landmarkproperties.com), or call us at 1 (888) 914-9661 PIN 493149.
            
            If you make a privacy request, we may take steps to verify your identity before responding to your request. You may designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. You may make such a designation by providing the agent with written permission to act on your behalf. As permitted by law, we may take steps to verify your own identity in response to a request even if you choose to use an agent.
            
            **Right to Know.** You have the right to know what Personal Information we have collected about you, which includes:
            
            1. The categories of Personal Information we have collected about you, including:
                1. The categories of sources from which the Personal Information was collected;
                2. Our business or commercial purposes for collecting, disclosing, or sharing Personal Information;
                3. The categories of recipients to which we disclose Personal Information;
                4. The categories of Personal Information that we sold, and for each category identified, the categories of third parties to which we sold that particular category of Personal Information;
                5. The categories of Personal Information that we disclosed for a business purpose, and for each category identified, the categories of recipients to which we disclosed that particular category of Personal Information.
            2. The specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you.
            
            **Right to Delete Your Personal Information.** You have the right to request that we delete Personal Information we collected from you, subject to certain exceptions.
            
            **Right to Correct Inaccurate Information.** If you believe the Personal Information we maintain about you is inaccurate, you have the right to request that we correct that information.
            
            **Right to Opt Out of Sales and Sharing of Personal Information.** You have the right to opt out of the sale of your Personal Information and to request that we do not share your Personal Information for cross-context behavioral advertising.
            
            **Right to Limit Use and Disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information.** We do not use or disclose sensitive Personal Information for purposes to which the right to limit use and disclosure applies under the CCPA.
            
            **Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of Your Privacy Rights.** If you choose to exercise any of your privacy rights under the CCPA, you also have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment by us.
            
        7. **Notice of Financial Incentives**
            
            From time to time, Landmark may offer a financial incentive such as a gift card or merchandise to consumers who choose to sign up for additional information about our properties, to register as an active sales lead, to visit one of our properties for a tour, or sign a lease. Participation in these activities requires you to provide some Personal Information, such as your Identifiers and Commercial Information. These incentives are designed to encourage participants to visit our properties or sign a lease.
            
            We have made a good faith estimate that the value of this Personal Information provided in connection with our incentives is equivalent to the relevant expenses related to the collection and retention of that Personal Information. Any difference in price or benefits provided to participants who receive an incentive is reasonably related to the value of the Personal Information provided.
            
            Should you wish to withdraw your participation in any program associated with a financial incentive as described above, please email us at [privacy@landmarkproperties.com](mailto:privacy@landmarkproperties.com), or call us at 1 (888) 914-9661 PIN 493149. Please visit our Privacy Policy \[link\] for more information about our privacy practices and how we may collect, use and disclose your Personal Information.
            
        8. **Third Party Marketing and Your California Privacy Rights**
            
            California’s “Shine the Light” law permits California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties or affiliates for their own direct marketing purposes. We do not share Personal Information with third parties or affiliates for those third parties’ or affiliates’ own direct marketing purposes. Californians may request information about our compliance with this law by contacting us as provided below.
            
        9. **Contact Us**
            
            For more information on your California privacy rights please email us at [privacy@landmarkproperties.com](mailto:privacy@landmarkproperties.com), or call us at 1 (888) 914-9661 PIN 493149.
            
    2. **Nevada**
        
        Although we do not “sell” “covered information” of Nevada “consumers” as those terms are defined by Chapter 603A of the Nevada Revised Statutes, you may contact us [here](mailto:privacy@landmarkproperties.com) and register an e-mail contact address for us to provide you notice in the event we should do so in the future, at which point you will have an opportunity to be verified and exercise your opt-out rights under that law. Contact us in the same manner to update your contact email for notices. Changing your email elsewhere (e.g., informational requests, account information, etc.) will not update your Nevada notice contact information. It is your responsibility to keep your notice contact information current.
        
    3. **Connecticut**
        
        Connecticut law requires any person or entity that collects Social Security numbers from Connecticut residents in the course of business to create a privacy protection policy and to publish or display it publicly. It is our policy to protect the confidentiality of Social Security numbers in our possession from misuse and improper disclosure by maintaining and enforcing policies and physical and electronic safeguards against misuse and improper disclosure. Unlawful disclosure of Social Security numbers is prohibited, and access to them is limited to personnel who need access to such information in order to perform their job functions.
        
13. **Changes to This Privacy Policy**
    
    We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy prospectively effective upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy and your use of our Service indicates your consent to the privacy policy posted at the time of use. However, we will not treat your previously collected Landmark Properties-Collected PII, to the extent it is not collected under the new privacy policy, in a manner materially different than represented at the time it was collected without your consent. To the extent any provision of this Privacy Policy is found by a competent tribunal to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be severed to the extent necessary for the remainder to be valid and enforceable.
    
14. **Contact Landmark Properties**
    
    If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Landmark Properties [here](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/contact-us/) or at 315 Oconee Street Athens, GA 30601 (Attention: Legal Department).
    
    _© Landmark Properties 2023. All Rights Reserved._

**Table of Contents**

Click on the links to navigate to the sections:

1. [Information We Collect](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#info-we-collect)
    
    1. [Information about You that You Provide](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#info-you-provide)
    2. [Information Collected Automatically](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#info-collected-auto)
    3. [Information Landmark Properties Collects From Other Sources](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#info-from-other-sources)
2. [How We Use The Information We Obtain](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#how-we-use)
3. [Information We Disclose to Third Parties](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#info-we-share)
4. [Sweepstakes, Contests, and Promotions](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#sweepestakes-contests)
5. [Third-Party Content and Services](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#third-party-content)
6. [Analytics](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#analytics-tracking-tech)
7. [Data Security and Monitoring](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#data-security)
8. [International Transfer](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#international-transfer)
9. [Children’s Privacy](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#children-privacy)
10. [Accessing and Changing Information](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#accessing-and-changing-information)
11. [Choices: Tracking and Communications Options](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#choices-options)
    
    1. [Tracking Technologies Generally](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#tracking-technologies-generally)
    2. [Communications](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#communications)
12. [State Notices](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#state-notices)
    
    1. [California Residents](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#california-residents)
    2. [Nevada Residents](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#nevada-residents)
    3. [Connecticut Privacy Notice](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#connecticut-privacy-policy)
13. [Changes to this Privacy Policy](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#changes-to-privacy-policy)
14. [Contact Landmark Properties](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#contact-landmark-properties)

**Landmark Properties California Applicant Privacy Notice**

The purpose of this California Applicant Privacy Notice (“**Applicant Notice**”) is to inform job applicants of Landmark Properties, its affiliates, and subsidiaries (“**Landmark**”) who are residents of the State of California (“**Applicants**” or “**you**”) of the categories of Personal Information we may collect about them and how we use their Personal Information. This Applicant Notice is provided pursuant to the California Consumer Privacy Act, as amended (the “**CCPA**”), and should be read in conjunction with all other policies that govern your relationship with us.

As used in this Applicant Notice, the term “**Personal Information**” means information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with Applicants. Personal Information does not include information that is publicly available, de-identified, or aggregated.

Unless otherwise noted, the disclosures herein cover our activities in the twelve (12) months preceding the Effective Date, as well as our current practices.

**Table of Contents**

1. [Collection, Use, and Disclosure of Personal Information](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#collection-use-and-disclosure-of-personal-information)
2. [Sources of Personal Information](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#sources-of-personal-information)
3. [Disclosing Your Personal Information](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#disclosing-your-personal-information)
4. [Selling or Sharing of Your Personal Information](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#selling-or-sharing-of-your-personal-information)
5. [How Long We Keep Your Personal Information](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#how-long-we-keep-your-personal-information)
6. [California Privacy Rights](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#california-privacy-rights)
7. [How to Contact Us](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/privacy-policy/#how-to-contact-us)

1. **Collection, Use, and Disclosure of Personal Information**
    
    Landmark may collect, use, and disclose Personal Information for business purposes consistent with applicable laws as identified below. Where we transfer applicable Personal Information to recipients, such as our service providers, we do so for the same business purposes described below. These examples may vary depending on the nature of your interactions with us.
    
    | **Category of Personal Information** | **Purposes for Collection, Use, or Disclosure** | **Categories of Recipients to whom Personal Information is Disclosed** |
    | --- | --- | --- |
    | **Identifiers** including name, alias, postal address, IP address, email address, or other similar identifiers | * To process job applications and maintain records<br>* To assess qualifications for a particular job or task<br>* To complete activities related to recruiting, onboarding, and employment referrals<br>* To enable you to register an account with us<br>* To improve our websites<br>* To recommend potential jobs for you<br>* To verify your identity and stated credentials<br>* To undertake activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of our systems and services, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance our systems and services | * Data analytics providers<br>* Background check vendors<br>* Information technology vendors |
    | **Personal Information described in Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)**, including your name, address, telephone number, education, employment, and employment history | * To process job applications and maintain records<br>* To assess qualifications for a particular job or task<br>* To complete activities related to recruiting, onboarding, and employment referrals<br>* To enable you to register an account with us<br>* To improve our websites<br>* To recommend potential jobs for you<br>* To verify your identity and stated credentials<br>* To undertake activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of our systems and services, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance our systems and services | * Data analytics providers<br>* Background check vendors<br>* Information technology vendors |
    | **Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law**, including race and ethnicity | * To comply with applicable laws and regulations | * State or federal government agencies |
    | **Internet or other electronic network activity information**, including network traffic data, job search history, and information regarding your interactions with our websites | * To ensure and improve the security, integrity, and functionality of our websites<br>* To offer you information and employment-related opportunities | * Data analytics providers<br>* Information technology vendors |
    | **Sensory Information**, including audio and/or visual information, such as: closed- circuit images/video and audio recordings as may relate to your application | * To manage the security of our premises and systems<br>* To detect and prevent fraud against you and/or us | * Security providers<br>* Information technology vendors |
    | **Professional or employment-related information**, including: Skills, qualifications, work experience, references, recommendations, and other information included in a resume, CV, application form, or cover letter; Answers to behavioral or other screening questions in an interview; Information contained in any personal webpages or documents you choose to share with us; Information relating to professional licenses, training, disciplinary actions, and membership in professional organizations; Information relating to membership in civic organizations you may provide to us. | * To open and maintain your application records<br>* To assess your eligibility for employment<br>* To assess qualifications for a particular job or task<br>* To comply with applicable laws and regulations<br>* To manage the workplace safety and security<br>* To verify your identity and stated credentials | * Background check providers, including vendors and state or federal government agencies |
    | **Non-public education Information**, including school(s) attended, and other information relating to your secondary and post-secondary education | * To open and maintain your application records<br>* To assess your eligibility for employment<br>* To assess qualifications for a particular job or task<br>* To comply with applicable laws and regulation<br>* To manage the workplace safety and security<br>* To verify your identity and stated credentials | * Background check providers, including vendors and state or federal government agencies |
    | **Inferences** used to create a profile reflecting your skills abilities, and aptitudes | * We will only use this information for recruitment efforts and will not impact your current application or future employment with us. | * N/A |
    | **Other Categories of Personal Information**, including national identification information (citizenship, immigration, visa status, and work authorization information), criminal records information (such as results of background checks), languages spoken, and drug screening results | * To open and maintain your application records<br>* To assess your eligibility for employment<br>* To assess qualifications for a particular job or task<br>* To comply with applicable laws and regulations<br>* To manage the workplace safety and security<br>* To verify your identity and stated credentials<br>* Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration<br>* Undertaking activities to verify, maintain, improve, upgrade, or enhance the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned/manufactured/controlled by Landmark | * Background check providers, including vendors and state or federal government agencies<br>* State or federal government agencies related to confirmation of national identification information and criminal records information |
    
2. **Sources of Personal Information**
    
    We may collect the Personal Information identified above from the following sources:
    
    * **Directly from you**. For example, during the application process and throughout your interactions with us, including through our IT systems, company forms, and other processes where you submit information to us.
    * **Automatically when using our electronic systems**. For example, we may collect your usage history when you use our websites, systems, and applications.
    * **Landmark affiliates**. We receive Personal Information from Landmark affiliates, as permitted, to enable us to manage our business and workforce.
    * **Automatically when you visit our facilities**. For example, security camera footage.
    * **Service providers**. For example, we may receive your resume and other application information from entities such as LinkedIn or other job boards or job posting aggregates.
3. **Disclosing Your Personal Information**
    
    We may disclose each of the categories of Personal Information identified above to the respectively identified categories of recipients for operational or business purposes consistent with the purposes for collection or use designated, as is reasonably necessary and proportionate to achieve those purposes, or for another purpose that is compatible with the context in which the Personal Information was collected including, but not limited to:
    
    * Helping to ensure security and integrity;
    * Debugging, repairing, and improving functionality;
    * Short-term, transient use;
    * Performing services on our behalf;
    * Internal research for technological development; and
    * Verifying quality and/or safety.
    
    In addition to the other purposes for collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information described in this Applicant Notice, we may collect, use, and disclose Personal Information as required by law, regulation or court order; to respond to governmental and/or law enforcement requests; to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with our or others’ rights or property; to support any actual or threatened claim, defense or declaration in a case or before any jurisdictional and/or administrative authority, arbitration or mediation panel; or in connection with disciplinary actions/investigations. Likewise, we may use and disclose Personal Information to other parties in connection with a sale, assignment, merger, reorganization, or other transfer of our Company.
    
4. **Selling or Sharing of Your Personal Information**
    
    We do not sell your Personal Information or share it for cross-context behavioral advertising.
    
5. **How Long We Keep Your Personal Information**
    
    We generally maintain Personal Information according to our retention obligations and policies, operational business purposes, and other legal and regulatory requirements. We discard this Personal Information when reasonably practicable.
    
    We keep the categories of Personal Information described above for as long as is necessary for the purposes described in this Applicant Notice or otherwise authorized by law. This generally means holding the information for as long as one of the following apply:
    
    * Your Personal Information is reasonably necessary to manage our operations, to manage your relationship with us, or to satisfy another purpose for which we collected it;
    * Your Personal Information is reasonably necessary to carry out a disclosed purpose that is reasonably compatible with the context in which it was collected;
    * Your Personal Information is reasonably required to protect or defend our rights or property (which will generally relate to applicable laws that limit actions in a particular case);
    * We are otherwise required or permitted to keep your Personal Information by applicable laws or regulations.
    
    Where your Personal Information is used for more than one purpose, we will retain it until the purpose with the latest period expires.
    
6. **California Privacy Rights**
    
    If you are a resident of California, you have the right to submit certain requests relating to your Personal Information as described below. To exercise any of these rights, please submit a request through our [Privacy Web Form (onetrust.com)](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/0680dcba-1e23-43d2-8969-1b3ed9c36860/1257ef14-eb99-4a7f-b9da-cf2f1838e626) email us at [privacy@landmarkproperties.com](mailto:privacy@landmarkproperties.com), or call us at 1 (888) 914-9661 PIN 493149
    
    If you make a privacy request, we may take steps to verify your identity before responding to your request. You may designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. You may make such a designation by providing the agent with written permission to act on your behalf. As permitted by law, we may take steps to verify your own identity in response to a request even if you choose to use an agent.
    
    **Right to Opt Out of the Sale and Sharing of Your Personal Information**. We do not sell or share Personal Information for purposes to which the right to limit use and disclosure applies under the CCPA
    
    **Right to Limit Use and Disclosure of Your Sensitive Personal Information.** We do not collect, use, or disclose sensitive Personal Information for purposes to which the right to limit use and disclosure applies under the CCPA.
    
    **Right to Know**. You have the right to know what Personal Information we have collected about you, which includes:
    
    1. The categories of Personal Information we have collected about you, including:
        1. The categories of sources from which the Personal Information was collected;
        2. Our business purposes for collecting or disclosing Personal Information;
        3. The categories of recipients to which we disclose Personal Information;
        4. The categories of Personal Information that we disclosed for a business purpose, and for each category identified, the categories of recipients to which we disclosed that particular category of Personal Information.
    2. The specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you.
    
    **Right to Delete Your Personal Information**. You have the right to request that we delete Personal Information we collected from you, subject to certain exceptions.
    
    **Right to Correct Inaccurate Information**. If you believe that Personal Information we maintain about you is inaccurate, you have the right to request that we correct that information.
    
    **Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of Your Privacy Rights**. If you choose to exercise any of your privacy rights under the CCPA, you also have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment by us, including retaliation against you as an Applicant.
    
7. **How to Contact Us**
    
    If you have any questions about how Landmark handles your Personal Information or if you need to access this Applicant Notice in an alternative format or language, please contact us at:
    
    Phone: 1 (888) 914-9661 PIN 493149
    
    Email: [privacy@landmarkproperties.com](mailto:privacy@landmarkproperties.com)

Who We Are

What We Do

Our Portfolio

Contact

315 Oconee Street  
Athens, GA 30601

Landmark Properties is a fully integrated real estate firm specializing in consulting, investment, development, construction and management of high quality residential  communities. Backed by a deep understanding of the markets, a commitment to quality and a strong track record of success, Landmark is responsible for some of the premier student housing communities in the nation.

* CA Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information

Copyright © 2024 All Rights Reserved | [Employee Resources](https://www.landmarkproperties.com/employee-resources/)

[Website Design & Marketing](https://www.jumpem.com/ "Website Design & Marketing") By JUMPEM

Send Us A Message

×

<a href="https://jumpem.wufoo.com/forms/z1h6xpee0bvqy5f/">Fill out my Wufoo form!</a>
